https://www.livefoods.co.uk/privacy.php?osCsid=ff11436d20908a6cc217cbb5ecb66ce4

My Account Log In RegisterMy AccountMy OrdersMy Address BookMy PasswordMy Wish List 0 item(s) 0 item(s), £0.00 0 item(s) 0 item(s), £0.00 My Account Log In RegisterMy AccountMy OrdersMy Address BookMy PasswordMy Wish ListToggle NavigationReptile & Aquatic FoodLivefood Prepack TubsLivefood Mega TubsLivefood in Half BulkLivefood in BulkBulk MealwormsFish FoodsFrozen FoodsBug Gel, Cricket FoodPre-prepared FoodsTortoise and Turtle FoodFeeding & Water BowlsWaterfalls Foggers Misters PumpsWater Falls & DrippersFoggers & MistersRainfall Systems & SprayersPumps
& FiltersFeeding & Water BowlsVitamins CleaningDisinfectants CleaningVitamins and MineralsHealth & Water TreatmentsReptile Health ProductsAquatic Health & Water TreatmentReptile LightingLED LightingLow Voltage SystemsWhite Day Spot LampsGreen and Blue Spot LampsRed Night Spot LampsDay Light BulbsNight Light BulbsDay Light UVB TubesJungle UVB Light TubesDesert UVB Light TubesAquatic Light TubesBird Lighting and AccessoriesStarters / ControllersCombined UV and HeatCompact BulbsFittings and ReflectorsHeat and Light GuardsLighting Hoods / CanopiesReptile HeatingNight Spot LightsDay Spot LightsNight BulbsDay BulbsCeramic HeatersReptile Heat MatsVivarium Heat StripsCombined UV HeatFittings and ReflectorsLighting HoodsReptile Heating GuardsMeasure Temperature HumidityControl TemperatureVivarium DecorHanging Plastic PlantsHanging Silk PlantsRain Forest PlantsGround cover plantsCaves and HidesDecor ItemsVivarium BackgroundsWater Bowls and Food DishesSubstratesMats / Cage CarpetsMineral Based SubstratesVegetable Based SubstratesVivariums / TerrariumsMesh TerrariumsPlastic tanks and TerrariumsVivarium AccessoriesReptile Handling / SparesMiscellaneousReplacement Parts/SparesHandling and ToolsGifts and NoveltiesInvertebrate PetsPrivacy NoticeLivefood UK Ltd. knows that you care how information about you is used and shared,
and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.
By visiting Livefood UK Ltd., you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
This privacy notice (together with our terms of use) aims to give you information on how Livefood UK Ltd. collects and processes your personal data through your use of this website, including any data you may provide through this website when you sign up to our newsletter or purchase a product.
This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.
It is important that you read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.CONTROLLER
Livefood UK Ltd. is the controller and responsible for your personal data (collectively referred to as "we", "us" or "our" in this privacy notice).
We have appointed a data protection officer who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice.
If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the data protection officer using the details set out below.
You have the right to request what information we hold on you and to request that information be removed.
Our full details are:
Full name of legal entity: Livefood UK Ltd.
Name or title of data protection officer: Steve Rolfe
Email address: steve@livefood.co.uk
Postal address:
Livefood UK Ltd.
The Acres Gills Lane
Rooks Bridge
Somerset
BS26 2TZ
Telephone number: 01934 750743
You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk).
We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.
This version was last updated on 25th May 2018.What Personal Information About Customers Does Livefood UK Ltd. Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at
Livefood UK Ltd.. Here are the types of information we gather.Information You Give Us:
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.
You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our
features, for instance if you do not provide your postal address we will not be able to send your goods, if you do not provide an email address we will not be able to send you tracking information and let you know when your order has been despatched. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests and communicating with you.Automatic Information:
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like most Web sites,
we use "cookies" E-mail Communications:
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from
Livefood UK Ltd. if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive promotional e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this by selecting unsubscribed in the newsletters menu.What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer\'s hard drive through your Web browser to enable
our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts for
storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies,
how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Livefood UK Ltd.\'s coolest features, and we recommend that
you leave them turned on.Does Livefood UK Ltd. Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to
others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries Livefood UK Ltd. controls and as described below.Agents:
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf.
Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing
customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for
other purposes.Promotional Offers:
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Livefood UK Ltd. customers. If you do not want to receive such offers,
please adjust your account newsletter preference as that is how we will send out our promotions.Business Transfers:
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information
generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Livefood UK Ltd., or substantially
all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.Protection of Livefood UK Ltd. and Others:
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law;
enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other
agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Livefood UK Ltd., our users, or others. This includes exchanging
information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.With Your Consent:
(In accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 25th May 2018) - We do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam), we will only contact you with information of special offers and promotions if you have specifically asked to be kept informed by subscribing to our mailing list. We will never give your email address to any 3rd parties. How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information
you input. Livefood UK Ltd. conforms with the requirements of the Data Protection Act, 1998 and EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.
Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.What Information Can I Access?
Livefood UK Ltd. gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and,
in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.Your AccountWhat Choices Do I Have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase
or to take advantage of such Livefood UK Ltd. features as Automatic login, and permanent shopping carts. You can add or
update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "My Account" pages. When you update information, we
usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this in the newsletter
menu.Children
Livefood UK Ltd. does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children\'s products for purchase by adults.
If you are under 18, you may use Livefood UK Ltd. only with involvement of a parent or guardian.Information You Give Us
You provide most such information when you search, buy,
post, participate in a contest or questionnaire,
or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product or make an order provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one
e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or
a contest entry form.
As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, e-mail and phone number;
people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and phone number.Automatic Information
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your
computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type
and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to,
through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for.'
DATA SECURITY
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.
Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
No fee usually required
You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.
What we may need from you
We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.
Time limit to respond
We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.
YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS
Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. Please click on the links below to find out more about these rights:
Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a "data subject access request"). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.
Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.
Object to processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.
Request restriction of processing of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios:
(a) if you want us to establish the data's accuracy;
(b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it;
(c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or
(d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.
Request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.
Withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
CategoriesReptile & Aquatic FoodLivefood Prepack TubsLivefood Mega TubsLivefood in Half BulkLivefood in BulkBulk MealwormsFish FoodsFrozen FoodsBug Gel, Cricket FoodPre-prepared FoodsTortoise and Turtle FoodFeeding & Water BowlsWaterfalls Foggers Misters PumpsWater Falls & DrippersFoggers & MistersRainfall Systems & SprayersPumps
& FiltersFeeding & Water BowlsVitamins CleaningDisinfectants CleaningVitamins and MineralsHealth & Water TreatmentsReptile Health ProductsAquatic Health & Water TreatmentReptile LightingLED LightingLow Voltage SystemsWhite Day Spot LampsGreen and Blue Spot LampsRed Night Spot LampsDay Light BulbsNight Light BulbsDay Light UVB TubesJungle UVB Light TubesDesert UVB Light TubesAquatic Light TubesBird Lighting and AccessoriesStarters / ControllersCombined UV and HeatCompact BulbsFittings and ReflectorsHeat and Light GuardsLighting Hoods / CanopiesReptile HeatingNight Spot LightsDay Spot LightsNight BulbsDay BulbsCeramic HeatersReptile Heat MatsVivarium Heat StripsCombined UV HeatFittings and ReflectorsLighting HoodsReptile Heating GuardsMeasure Temperature HumidityControl TemperatureVivarium DecorHanging Plastic PlantsHanging Silk PlantsRain Forest PlantsGround cover plantsCaves and HidesDecor ItemsVivarium BackgroundsWater Bowls and Food DishesSubstratesMats / Cage CarpetsMineral Based SubstratesVegetable Based SubstratesVivariums / TerrariumsMesh TerrariumsPlastic tanks and TerrariumsVivarium AccessoriesReptile Handling / SparesMiscellaneousReplacement Parts/SparesHandling and ToolsGifts and NoveltiesInvertebrate PetsSpecialsVacuum Packed Crickets (Reptile Food) 500-1000£10.90£6.00ReviewsFirst time using this site. Arrived fairly quickly (have to ...Wish ListYour Wish List is empty.What's New?Reptile Systems Mercury Vapour lamp 100w£35.19
